boramilu.com 2015-06-21

# Privacy Policy | boramilu.com

Information Collection and Use 

When you sign up for an account boramilu.com, boramilu.com using other products or services, access to boramilu.com pages, or participate in promotions and sweepstakes, boramilu.com will collect your personally identifiable information. boramilu.com also collect personally identifiable information from business partners.   
When you register boramilu.com account, we will ask you for your name, email address, interests, date of birth, gender, personal home and personal introduction. Once you have successfully registered with boramilu.com and log server, we will be able to identify you.   
boramilu.com will automatically receive and record information that your browser and the server logs, including your IP address, boramilu.com cookie information and the page you are recording needs.   
boramilu.com, such information will be used to improve the video quality of service you provide.

Information disclosure and sharing 

boramilu.com will not share your personally identifiable information display, rented or sold to anyone  
The following exceptions:   
Only disclose your personal information to provide you requested products and services;   
We need to represent our company to provide products or services to provide information (Unless we notify you otherwise, these companies have no right to use your personally identifiable information);   
We need to obey the court summons, legal order or comply with legal process;   
We found that you violated the terms of service of boramilu.com, boramilu.com of the global village Terms of Use or any other products and services. 

Special Note for Parents

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, boramilu.com does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Web Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Web Site is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Web Site at any time or in any manner. If boramilu.com learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Web Site without verified parental consent, then boramilu.com will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

HTML e-mail 

boramilu.com in general practice is to send HTML e-mail message form (including image-mail) when combined with beacon, used to calculate the number of messages have been opened.   
In general, electronic images will be regarded as part of the website, including banner ads, you can use as a beacon. So in boramilu.com are also placed ads can add beacon.   
boramilu.com to track specific usage behavior. Web beacons to collect information from the user to learn how to use our products, and to provide more accurate reporting and enhance marketing effectiveness.   

Cookies

boramilu.com will be set up or access boramilu.com Cookie on your computer. boramilu.com allow those companies publish advertisements on our website to access settings on the user's computer or Cookie. Other companies according to their own privacy policies, not this Policy Cookie, they can not access boramilu.com of Cookie. boramilu.com during its products and services related work, will use the network to our website to extract Beacon Cookie. 

Permission to edit personal account information and preferences 

boramilu.com gives you the right to edit boramilu.com account information and preferences at any time, including whether to accept the latest product information provided in boramilu.com.

Revised and republished 2014
